this a lot of optimism as countries
around the region start opening up what
kind of opportunities are you seeing
what kind of demand are you looking at
in terms of insurance demand so we're
seeing a real uptick in demand for
healthcare products I think covert has
made people far more aware of their
personal vulnerabilities in terms of
health matters that's the first thing
and the second thing with all the
volatility in the market we're seeing
people really looking for a different
way to save where there may be
guarantees that insurance company can
provide when the Market's always going
up everybody thinks they're a Warren
Buffett when the mock is highly volatile
actually everybody wants a little bit of
certainty a little bit of comfort and
that's when they start pivoting towards
insurance companies so we see it as an
opportunity for both health and in terms
of the savings an uptick 20 30 off take
is that a fair assumption so what we're
seeing is in terms of number of policies
that we're selling so for example last
year we saw 41 increase in the number of
health and protection policies being
sold the average case size was down
partly due to the element of the
uncertainty in the economy and people's
uncertainties and lack of appetite to
connect and to commit maybe four or five
or ten year policy so they're having
slightly shorter duration policies but
really everybody's saying I want to get
some cover
so with increasing inflation and with
uncertainty in the in the economies we
have adjusted our products to be able to
provide more bite size more
minimal cost affordable covers so for
example in Vietnam you can get cover for
cancer for under a dollar U.S dollar a
month so those are some of the products
that were started to roll out in some of
our markets to adjust to the environment
this is a highly competitive industry
it's been disrupted heavily by fintechs
wanting uh I guess a slice of the pie
how are you responding to that so one of
the key things that we've found is is
the the pandemic over the last few years
has accelerated all the traditional
players digital agendas it's enabled us
as an organization it's enabled our
people it's enabled regulators and it's
enabled our agents and our customers to
engage with us in a very different way
so the organization is transformed in a
far great fashion then we probably
thought we were going to be able to
achieve ourselves left our own devices
so we've transformed more quickly we've
transformed in a more extensive Fashion
on a digital basis so that we sell more
products we're doing more Underground
writing that's almost straight through
fully automated and if we don't the
small Nimble fintech players are going
to eat our lunch so it's important that
we adjust and that we're agile in our
response credential has talked about
pivoting to Asia give us a sense of the
Manpower are you shifting perhaps the
workforce from the UK to Asia what do
you have in mind what's the strategy
there so last year we finished our
financial restructuring in terms of
spinning off our U.S business so now
we're pure Asia Africa play we're in 15
markets in Asia eight markets in in
Africa and we have about 14 and a half
thousand employees in Asia and we have
over half a million agents in Asia and
Africa
we are reducing the size and scale of
our London operation and we're bringing
more people to Asia more roles to Asia
so we've got additional people in Hong
Kong we've got additional people in
Singapore
um and all of that is reflecting that as
our stakeholders pivot more and more
towards Asia we want the right expertise
in Asia to be able to deal with it in
the right time zone but also probably
most importantly with the right context
of the markets and what's happening in
the market China is a big
about perhaps a joint venture a JV we're
sitting back into this wealth management
can you confirm if there's such plan
there's such talks so we have an
existing JV with citic it's been in
place now for 22 years it's very very
successful we've made no secret of the
fact that we'd love to earn the other 50
percent
but to do a transaction with leader
willings a willing seller at this stage
we're looking to grow the business make
it as successful as possible in the view
that as and when an opportunity arises
to buy the balance we will be able to
then buy a bigger more successful
business in the future China is a very
exciting market for us the level of
penetration and insurance in that market
is very low it's about three and a half
percent so there's so much more that we
can do on a on a kind of a Health and
Care and savings product pensions is a
huge opportunity in China the vast
majority of the population have a very
very low level of pension and with the
Asian demographic it makes it a very
real opportunity for us and others in
the market